Daniel Yankelovich Papers
© 2002 University of Connecticut
- Series I: Writings,undated, 1947-1992
  - Subseries B: Books,undated, 1947-1991
    - Coming to Public Judgment: Making Democracy Work in a Complex World
      - Typescript draft, introduction and part III, edited, 1989-1990
        - Chapter 17, "Searching for Public Judgment", 1990 Jan (Box 8:237)
        - Chapter 18, "You Can Argue With Einstein", 1990 Jan (Box 8:238)
      - Typescript draft, part III, 1990 Jan
        - Chapter 14, "Epistemological Anxiety", 1990 Jan (Box 8:239)
        - Chapter 15, "Defining Objectivism", 1990 Jan (Box 8:240)
        - Chapter 16, "Deconstructing Objectivism", 1990 Jan (Box 8:241)
        - Chapter 17, "Searching for Public Judgment", 1990 Jan (Box 8:242)
        - Chapter 18, "You Can Argue With Einstein", 1990 Jan (Box 8:243)
      - Typescript draft, Introduction and parts I, II, III, edited, 1990 Jan
        - Introduction, "Crowding Out the Public", 1990 Jan (Box 9:244)
        - Chapter 1, "A Missing Concept", 1990 Jan (Box 9:245)
        - Chapter 2, "What is Quality in Public Opinion?", 1990 Jan (Box 9:246)
        - Chapter 3, "Mass Opinion vs. Public Judgment", 1990 Jan (Box 9:247)
        - Chapter 4, "Knowledge vs. Opinion", 1990 Jan (Box 9:248)
        - Chapter 5, "The Bumpy Road From Mass Opinion to Public Judgment", 1990 Jan (Box 9:249)
        - Chapter 6, "Consciousness Raising", 1990 Jan (Box 9:250)
        - Chapter 7, "Transition Obstacles", 1990 Jan (Box 9:251)
        - Chapter 8, "The Expert-Public Gap", 1990 Jan (Box 9:252)
        - Chapter 9, "The Competitiveness Issue", 1990 Jan (Box 9:253)
        - Chapter 10, "From Minutes to Centuries", 1990 Jan (Box 9:254)
        - Chapter 11, "The Cold War: End It or Not?", 1990 Jan (Box 9:255)
        - Chapter 12 (no title), 1990 Jan (Box 9:256)
        - Chapter 13, "Ten Rules For Resolution", 1990 Jan (Box 9:257)
        - Chapter 14, "Epistemological Anxiety", 1990 Jan (Box 9:258)
        - Chapter 15, "Defining Objectivism", 1990 Jan (Box 9:259)
        - Chapter 16, "Deconstructing Objectivism", 1990 Jan (Box 9:260)
        - Chapter 17, "Searching for Public Judgment", 1990 Jan (Box 9:261)
        - Chapter 18, "You Can Argue With Einstein", 1990 Jan (Box 9:262)
      - Typescript draft, 1990 Jan
        - Introductory material and bibliography, 1990 Jan (Box 9:263)
        - Chapter 1, "A Missing Concept", 1990 Jan (Box 9:264)
        - Chapter 2, "What is Quality in Public Opinion?", 1990 Jan (Box 9:265)
        - Chapter 3, "Mass Opinion vs. Public Judgment", 1990 Jan (Box 9:266)
        - Chapter 4, "Knowledge vs. Opinion", 1990 Jan (Box 9:267)
        - Chapter 5, "The Bumpy Road From Mass Opinion to Public Judgment", 1990 Jan (Box 9:268)
        - Chapter 6, "Consciousness Raising", 1990 Jan (Box 9:269)
        - Chapter 7, "Transition Obstacles", 1990 Jan (Box 9:270)
        - Chapter 8, "The Expert-Public Gap", 1990 Jan (Box 9:271)
        - Chapter 9, "The Competitiveness Issue", 1990 Jan (Box 9:272)
        - Chapter 10, "From Minutes to Centuries", 1990 Jan (Box 9:273)
        - Chapter 11, "The Cold War: End It or Not?", 1990 Jan (Box 10:274)
        - Chapter 12, "An Experiment in Working Through", 1990 Jan (Box 10:275)
        - Chapter 13, "Ten Rules For Resolution", 1990 Jan (Box 10:276)
        - Chapter 14, "Epistemological Anxiety", 1990 Jan (Box 10:277)
        - Chapter 15, "Defining Objectivism", 1990 Jan (Box 10:278)
        - Chapter 16, "Deconstructing Objectivism", 1990 Jan (Box 10:279)
        - Chapter 17, "Searching for Public Judgment", 1990 Jan (Box 10:280)
        - Chapter 18, "You Can Argue With Einstein", 1990 Jan (Box 10:281)
      - Typescript draft, edited, 1990 Jan 31
        - Introductory material and bibliography, 1990 Jan (Box 10:282)
        - Introduction, "Crowding the Public Out", 1990 Jan (Box 10:283)
        - Chapter 1, "A Missing Concept", 1990 Jan (Box 10:284)
        - Chapter 2, "What is Quality in Public Opinion?", 1990 Jan (Box 10:285)
        - Chapter 3, "Mass Opinion vs. Public Judgment", 1990 Jan (Box 10:286)
        - Chapter 4, "Knowledge vs. Opinion", 1990 Jan (Box 10:287)
        - Chapter 5, "The Bumpy Road From Mass Opinion to Public Judgment", 1990 Jan (Box 10:288)
        - Chapter 6, "Consciousness Raising", 1990 Jan (Box 10:289)
        - Chapter 7, "Transition Obstacles", 1990 Jan (Box 10:290)
        - Chapter 8, "The Expert-Public Gap", 1990 Jan (Box 10:291)
        - Chapter 9, "The Competitiveness Issue", 1990 Jan (Box 10:292)
        - Chapter 10, "From Minutes to Centuries", 1990 Jan (Box 10:293)
        - Chapter 11, "The Cold War: End It or Not?", 1990 Jan (Box 10:294)
        - Chapter 12, "An Experiment in Working Through", 1990 Jan (Box 10:295)
        - Chapter 13, "Ten Rules For Resolution", 1990 Jan (Box 10:296)
        - Chapter 14, "Epistemological Anxiety", 1990 Jan (Box 10:297)
        - Chapter 15, "Defining Objectivism", 1990 Jan (Box 10:298)
        - Chapter 16, "Deconstructing Objectivism", 1990 Jan (Box 10:299)
        - Chapter 17, "Searching for Public Judgment", 1990 Jan (Box 10:300)
        - Chapter 18, "You Can Argue With Einstein", 1990 Jan (Box 10:301)
      - Typescript draft, 1990 Feb (Box :)
        - Introduction, "Crowding Out the Public", 1990 Feb (Box 10:302)
        - Chapter 1, "A Missing Concept", 1990 Jan (Box 10:303)
        - Chapter 2, "What is Quality in Public Opinion?", 1990 Jan (Box 10:304)
        - Chapter 3, "Mass Opinion vs. Public Judgment", 1990 Jan (Box 10:305)
        - Chapter 4, "Knowledge vs. Opinion", 1990 Jan (Box 10:306)
        - Chapter 5, "The Bumpy Road From Mass Opinion to Public Judgment", 1990 Jan (Box 10:307)
        - Chapter 6, "Consciousness Raising", 1990 Jan (Box 10:308)
        - Chapter 7, "Transition Obstacles", 1990 Jan (Box 11:309)
        - Chapter 8, "The Expert-Public Gap", 1990 Jan (Box 11:310)
        - Chapter 9, "The Competitiveness Issue", 1990 Jan (Box 11:311)
        - Chapter 10, "From Minutes to Centuries", 1990 Jan (Box 11:312)
        - Chapter 11, "The Cold War: End It or Not?", 1990 Jan (Box 11:313)
        - Chapter 12, "An Experiment in Working Through", 1990 Jan (Box 11:314)
        - Chapter 13, "Ten Rules For Resolution", 1990 Jan (Box 11:315)
        - Chapter 14, "Epistemological Anxiety", 1990 Jan (Box 11:316)
        - Chapter 15, "Defining Objectivism", 1990 Jan (Box 11:317)
        - Chapter 16, "Deconstructing Objectivism", 1990 Jan (Box 11:318)
        - Chapter 17, "Searching for Public Judgment", 1990 Jan (Box 11:319)
        - Chapter 18, "You Can Argue With Einstein", 1990 Jan (Box 11:320)
        - Endnotes, 1990 Jan (Box 11:321)
        - Bibliography, 1990 Jan (Box 11:322)
      - Typescript semi-final draft, edited, 1990 Apr-May
        - Preface, 1990 May (Box 11:323)
        - Introduction, "Crowding Out the Public", 1990 Apr (Box 11:324)
        - Chapter 1, "A Missing Concept", 1990 Apr-May (Box 11:325)
        - Chapter 2, "What is Quality in Public Opinion?", 1990 Apr-May (Box 11:326)
        - Chapter 3, "Mass Opinion vs. Public Judgment", 1990 Apr (Box 11:327)
        - Chapter 4, "Knowledge vs. Opinion", 1990 Apr (Box 11:328)
        - Chapter 5, "The Bumpy Road From Mass Opinion to Public Judgment", 1990 May (Box 11:329)
        - Chapter 6, "Consciousness Raising", 1990 May (Box 11:330)
        - Chapter 7, "Transition Obstacles", 1990 May (Box 11:331)
        - Chapter 8, "The Expert-Public Gap", 1990 Apr-May (Box 11:332)
        - Chapter 9, "The Competitiveness Issue", 1990 May (Box 11:333)
        - Chapter 10, "From Minutes to Centuries", 1990 May (Box 11:334)
        - Chapter 11, "The End of the Cold War", 1990 Apr (Box 11:335)
        - Chapter 12, "An Experiment in Working Through", 1990 May (Box 11:336)
        - Chapter 13, "Ten Rules For Resolution", 1990 May (Box 11:337)
        - Chapter 14, "Epistemological Anxiety", 1990 May (Box 12:338)
        - Chapter 15, "Defining Objectivism", 1990 May (Box 12:339)
        - Chapter 16, "Deconstructing Objectivism", 1990 May (Box 12:340)
        - Chapter 17, "Searching for Public Judgment", 1990 May (Box 12:341)
        - Chapter 18, "You Can Argue With Einstein", 1990 May (Box 12:342)
        - Chapter 19, "A Sketch for Action", 1990 May (Box 12:343)
        - Endnotes and bibliography, 1990 May (Box 12:344)
      - Typescript draft, miscellaneous pages and endnotes, edited, [1990] (Box 12:345-346)
      - Book distribution, undated, 1991-1992 (Box 12:347)
      - Book jacket, 1990 (Box 12:348)
      - Book promotion, 1991 (Box 12:349)
      - Book reviews, 1991-1992 (Box 12:350)
      - Book reviews, 1989-1990 (Box 12:351)
      - Permission to publish chapter 9, 1990 Oct (Box 12:352)
      - Permission to publish chapter 18, 1990 Nov (Box 12:353)
      - Photograph of Yankelovich oration, undated (Box 12:354)
      - Quotes - requests, 1991 Mar (Box 12:355)
      - Quotes - received, 1991 (Box 12:356)
      - Reprint permission from USA Today, 1989-1990 (Box 12:357)
      - Syracuse University: manuscript preparation guidelines, 1989 (Box 12:358-359)
      - Syracuse University Press catalog, 1991 (Box 12:360)
      - Yankelovich, D., "Public Opinion, Public Judgment and America's Future: An Interview with Daniel Yankelovich," America's Agenda, 1991 Summer (Box 12:361)
    - Ego and Instinct: A New Philosophy for Psychoanalysis, with William Barrett, 1970
      - Summaries, 1970 (Box 12:362)
      - Typescript draft, Part I, "Freud and the Human Ego", Part II, "Freud's Heirs: The Ego Restored", [1967]
        - Chapter 1, "A Philosophical Neurosis, [1967] (Box 12:363)
        - Chapter 2, "Freud I: (Pre-1895) The Case of Miss Lucy", [1967] (Box 12:364)
        - Chapter 3, "Freud II: (1895-1922) The Discovery of Instinct", [1967] (Box 12:365)
        - Chapter 4, "Freud III: (The 1920s and after) `The Psychic Apparatus'", [1967] (Box 12:366)
        - Chapter 4, "Freud III: (The 1920s and after) 'The Psychic Apparatus'", [1967] (Box 13:367)
        - Chapter 5, "Postcript to Freud", [1967] (Box 13:368)
        - Chapter 6, "Heinz Hartmann, the Conserver", [1967] (Box 13:369)
        - Chapter 7, "Adding Epicycles", [1967] (Box 13:370)
        - Chapter 8, "The Question of Identity: Erik Erikson", [1967] (Box 13:371-372)
        - Chapter 9, "The Gambit Declined", [1967] (Box 13:373)
        - Chapter 10, "Four Strategies... And Stalemate", [1967] (Box 13:374)
      - Typescript draft, Part IV, "Toward a Reconstruction of the Metapsychology",1967
        - Chapter 15, "A Summary of the Current Situation", 1967 (Box 13:375)
        - Chapter 16, "Requirements for a Metapsychology", 1967 (Box 13:376)
        - Chapter 17, "The Core of the New Metapsychology", 1967 (Box 13:377)
        - Chapter 18, "The Core of the Reconstruction", 1967 (Box 13:378)
        - Chapter 19 missing
        - Chapter 20, "Instinct and Human Nature", 1967 (Box 13:379)
        - Chapter 21, "The Puzzle of Instinct", 1967 (Box 13:380)
        - Chapter 22, "Fitting the Puzzle Together", 1967 (Box 13:381)
        - Chapter 23, "Instinct Versus ID - Toward a Theory of Human Nature", 1967 (Box 13:382-383)
        - Chapter 24, "Forms of Freedom" and bibliography, 1967 (Box 13:384-385)
    - New Rules: Searching for Self-Fulfillment in a World Turned Upside Down,1981
      - Summary, thesis, undated, 1980 (Box 13:386)
      - Conceptual framework, undated, 1979 (Box 13:387)
      - Research material
        - Charts, undated (Box 13:388)
        - Clippings and articles, undated, 1974-1981 (Box 13:389)
        - Community and morality trends, 1977-1980 (Box 13:390)
        - Interviews
        - NOTE: In order to maintain the confidentiality of the interviewees, all interview material has been restricted until January 1, 2009. (boxes 14-17)
        - Interview abstractions: notecards,undated
          - Bolisovac, undated (Box 18:391)
          - Duple, undated (Box 18:392)
          - Hellman, undated (Box 18:393)
          - Sabectel, undated (Box 18:394)
        - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 18:395)
      - Notes
        - Chapter 1, undated (Box 18:396)
        - Cultural Revolution/part II, undated, 1979 May (Box 18:397)
        - Norms, undated (Box 18:398)
        - Notecards, undated (Box 18:399)
        - Notecards, undated, 1978 (Box 18:400-407)
        - Psycho-social, undated (Box 18:408)
        - Social change, undated (Box 18:409)
        - Success, undated (Box 18:410)
      - Dictations: audio tapes
        - Chapter 1, 3, 1979 Feb (Box 18:411)
        - Chapter 4, "Success vs. Self-fulfillment", 1979 Jul (Box 18:412)
        - Chapter 5, "Profile of Self-fulfillment Group", 1979 Jul (Box 18:413)
        - Introduction, 1978 Jan-Feb (Box 18:414)
        - Introduction, 1978 Feb (Box 19:415)
        - Motif, 1978 Feb (Box 19:416)
        - Section 4: thesis, 1978 Mar (Box 19:417)
        - Self-fulfillment book, 1978 Mar (Box 19:418)
        - Self-fulfillment book, [1978 Mar] (Box 19:419)
        - Yankelovich, D. and G. McEvoy, 1978 Oct (Box 19:420)
      - Unused material
        - Preface and introduction "remnants", 1980 (Box 19:421-422)
        - Part I "outtakes", [1980] (Box 19:423)
        - Part II, [1980] (Box 19:424-425)
        - Part II "outtakes", [1980] (Box 19:426)
        - Part III "outtakes", [1980] (Box 19:427-428)
        - Part IV "outtakes", [1980] (Box 19:429)
        - Part IV "outtakes", [1980] (Box 20:430)
      - Typescript final draft, incomplete, 1980 Nov
        - Title page, Dedication, Table of Contents, 1980 Nov (Box 20:431)
        - Preface, "The Giant Plates of Culture", 1980 Nov (Box 20:432)
        - Chapter 1, "Introduction: A Rare Event", 1980 Nov (Box 20:433)
        - Part I: "Flaws and Strengths"
          - Chapter 2, "The Threat of the Great Reversal", 1980 Nov (Box 20:434)
          - Chapter 3, "The Self-fulfillment Contradiction", 1980 Nov (Box 20:435)
          - Chapter 4, "The Promise Beneath the Guises", 1980 Nov (Box 20:436)
        - Part II: "Experiments in Self-fulfillment"
          - Chapter 5, "The Strong Form of the Self-fulfillment Prediction",1980 Nov (Box 20:437)
          - Chapter 6, "A Non-Rebel in Rebel's Clothing",1980 Nov (Box 20:438)
          - Chapter 7, "I Am My Own Work of Art",1980 Nov (Box 20:439)
          - Chapter 8, "New Norms: Being Obliged to Do What You Want to Do",1980 Nov (Box 20:440)
          - Chapter 9, "The Old Epochal Experience",1980 Nov (Box 20:441)
          - Chapter 10, "Otherwise the World is One Big Factory",1980 Nov (Box 20:442)
          - Chapter 11, "Feliciano's Bicycle",1980 Nov (Box 20:443)
          - Chapter 12, "With a Little Bit of Luck",1980 Nov (Box 20:444)
          - Chapter 12, "With a Little Bit of Luck",1980 Nov (Box 20:445)
        - Part IV: "An Ethic of Commitment"
          - Chapter 22, "Stepping Off Maslow's Escalator",1980 Nov (Box 20:446)
          - Chapter 23, "America's First Cultural Revolution",1980 Nov (Box 20:447)
          - Chapter 24, "Rewriting the Giving/Getting Compact",1980 Nov (Box 20:448)
          - Chapter 25, "Toward an Ethic of Commitment", incomplete,1980 Nov (Box 20:449)
      - Advertisements, undated, 1981 (Box 20:450)
      - Book reviews and commentaries, undated, 1981-1982 (Box 20:451-453)
      - Bound galleys list, 1981 (Box 20:454)
      - Holt, Bob, 1981 (Box 20:455)
      - Index file of book copy recipients, [1981] (Box 21)
      - Interview requests, undated, 1981 (Box 22:456)
      - Interview/presentation notes, [1981] (Box 22:457)
      - Interviews, 1981 (Box 22:458)
      - Fan letters, 1980-1982 (Box 22:459-461)
      - Thank you letters, 1981-1982 (Box 22:462-463)
      - Miscellaneous, 1981 (Box 22:464)
      - Contracts, 1981 (Box 22:465)
      - Publicity tour, 1981 (Box 22:466)
      - Random House Publishing, 1981 (Box 22:467)
    - Starting With the People, with Sidney Harman, 1988
      - Synopsis, 1987 Feb (Box 22:468)
      - Authors' summary, 1988 (Box 22:469)
      - Correspondence, 1981 (Box 22:470)
      - Correspondence: audio tape, 1981 (Box 22:471)
      - Correspondence, 1982-1986 (Box 22:472-476)
      - Correspondence, undated, 1987-1988 (Box 23:477-480)
      - Memoranda, 1981-1984 (Box 23:481-486)
      - New Framework Group
        - Statement of purpose, 1981-1982 (Box 23:487)
        - By-laws, [1981] (Box 23:488)
        - Organizational meeting, 1981 Sep 28 (Box 23:489)
        - Meeting, Steering Committee, 1981 Oct 20 (Box 23:490)
        - Meetings, 1981-1982 (Box 23:491-493)
        - Meeting, Steering Committee, 1982 Dec 10 (Box 23:494)
        - Members, 1981-1984 (Box 23:495)
        - Finances, 1982-1984 (Box 23:496)
        - Subgroup on Economic Policy, 1982-1983 (Box 23:497-498)
        - Subgroup on Defense and International Affairs, 1981-1983 (Box 23:499)
        - Subgroup on the Role of Government, 1982-1983 (Box 24:500-501)
        - Subgroup on Social Policy, 1982-1983 (Box 24:502)
          - Brown, Peter - draft papers,1983 (Box 24:503-504)
        - Notes on papers, undated (Box 24:505)
        - Aspin, Les - papers, 1982 (Box 24:506)
        - Letters of invitation, drafts, 1981-1982 (Box 24:507)
        - Letters to reviewers, [1982] (Box 24:508)
        - Chapter reviewers, [1982] (Box 24:509)
        - Mailing lists, 1983 (Box 24:510-512)
        - Miscellaneous, 1983 (Box 24:513)
        - Research material
          - Sawhill, Isabel, "Reaganomics in Retrospect" ,"Business Planning in the Eighties: The New Marketing Shape of American Corporations," by YSW, Inc., 1985 (Box 24:514)
          - Cohen, Richard., "Industrial Policy: Help or Harm for the American Economy," Public Agenda Foundation report, 1985 (Box 24:515)
          - Survey data concerning government and business, 1980-1985 (Box 24:516-519)
          - The Changing Situation of Workers and Their Unions," report by AFL-CIO, 1985 Feb (Box 24:520)
          - Merrifield, D. Bruce., "The Climate for Industrial Competitiveness", 1985 (Box 24:520)
          - Harman, Sidney., "Transcending the Strongman's Logic", 1983 (Box 24:521)
          - Council on Foreign Relations material, 1985 (Box 24:521)
          - Ekman, Bo., "Thoughts on Industrial Policy and Corporate Strategy-The Swedish Case," for Aspen Institute for Humanistic Studies, 1982 (Box 24:522)
          - Aspin, Les, untitled draft paper concerning Reagan challenge to Democrats, undated (Box 24:522)
        - Survey data concerning trade policy, 1987 (Box 25:523-524)
        - Correspondence, 1983-1984 (Box 25:525-526)
        - Yankelovich notes, undated, 1980-1984 (Box 25:527)
      - Regaining the Center (working title)
        - Discussion draft of chapters 1 and 3, 1984 Jan 6 (Box 25:528)
      - New Options (working title), Sidney Harman,, Les Aspin, and John Immerwahr
        - Meeting, 1984 Jun 28 (Box 25:529)
        - Presentation concerning framework of the book, 1984 Oct 31 (Box 25:530)
        - Drafts of book overview, 1984 Dec (Box 25:531)
        - Notes
          - General,[1983] (Box 25:532)
          - Notes for outline: chapter 3,1983 Dec (Box 25:533)
          - Chapter 1 and Introduction,1983-1984 (Box 25:534)
          - Health care notes by John Immerwahr,1984 Oct (Box 25:535)
          - Social contract,1983 (Box 25:536)
        - Typescript draft, Part I, introduction and chapter 1, [1983] (Box 25:537)
        - Typescript draft, introduction, 1984 Jun 10 (Box 25:538-539)
        - Typescript draft, chapter 1, "Managing the Economy: Critique of Conservatism", 1984 Jun 18 (Box 25:540)
        - Typescript draft, chapter 2, "Building Blocks of a Stakeholder Economic Strategy", 1984 Jun 14 (Box 25:541)
        - Typescript draft, chapter 3, "The Conservative Attack 1984 Jun 26 On the Welfare State", 1984 Jun 26 (Box 25:542)
        - Typescript draft, chapter 4, "Revising the Welfarre State" (written by John Immerwahr
          - Draft, edited by D. Yankelovich,1984 Jun 22 (Box 25:543)
          - Draft,1984 Jun 25 (Box 25:544)
          - Draft,1984 Jun 26 (Box 25:545)
          - Draft, edited by D. Yankelovich,1984 Jul 11 (Box 25:546)
        - Complete draft of book, 1984 Aug 9 (Box 25:547-548)
        - Typescript draft, chapter A2, "Framework Troubles", 1984 Dec 22 (Box 26:549)
        - Typescript draft, chapter B1, "Stalemate", 1985 Jan 16 (Box 26:550)
        - Typescript draft, chapter B2, "Causes", 1985 Jan 18 (Box 26:551)
        - Typescript draft, chapter B2, "Disarray", 1985 Jan 23 (Box 26:552)
        - Typescript draft, chapter D5, 1985 Mar (Box 26:553)
        - Typescript draft, Part II, introduction and chapters 1-3, 1985 Jun 25 (Box 26:554)
      - A New Political Framework (working title) with Les Aspin, Sidney Harman and John Immerwahr
        - Notes
          - Chapter 33,[1985] (Box 26:556)
          - Chapter 34,[1985] (Box 26:557)
          - Chapter 35, "Peaceful Contention",1985 (Box 26:558)
          - Chapter 35: notebook,[1985] (Box 26:559)
          - Chapter 37,[1985] (Box 26:560)
          - Final chapter,1986 (Box 26:561)
          - Reading notes: notebook,[1985] (Box 26:562)
          - National security policy: notebook,[1985] (Box 26:563)
          - Aspen/Yankelovich chapters,1985 Apr- May (Box 26:564)
          - Economics,1984 (Box 26:565)
        - Economics, 1984 Jan (Box 26:566-567)
        - Draft tables, "Managing the Economy", 1984 Jan (Box 26:568)
        - Outlines
          - Chapter 1, draft 1,1985 May (Box 26:569)
          - Chapter 2, draft 1,1985 May (Box 26:570)
          - Nuclear chapters,1985 May (Box 26:571)
          - Chapter 35, draft 2,1985 Aug (Box 26: 572)
        - Typescript draft, "Normalization", Typescript draft, Introduction, 1985 Apr (Box 26:573)
        - Typescript draft, Introduction
          - "Framework Troubles",1985 Apr (Box 27:574)
          - "Part II: Introduction",1985 Jul-Aug (Box 27:575)
          - Chapter 1, "Introduction",1985 Dec 26 (Box 27:576)
          - Chapter 1, "Introduction",1985 Dec 23 (Box 27:577)
        - Typescript draft, chapter 3, "The Loss of America's Competitive Advantage", 1986 Dec 29 (Box 27:578)
        - Typescript draft, chapter 4, "The Crisis of Competitive Vulnerability", 1985 Nov 5 (Box 27:579)
        - Typescript draft, chapter 4, "Boeskyism and Other Distractions", 1986 Nov 25 (Box 27:580)
        - Typescript draft, chapter 4, "A Flawed Framework (Boeskyism and Other Diversions)", 1986 Dec 31 (Box 27:581)
        - Typescript draft, chapter 5, "A Stakeholder Strategy", 1985 Dec (Box 27:582)
        - Typescript draft, chapter 6, "The Limits of 'Lean and Mean'", 1985 Nov 8 (Box 27:583)
        - Typescript draft, chapter 6, "A New Wave of Energy", 1985 Dec (Box 27:584)
        - Typescript draft, chapter 7, "The Japanese Strategic Concept", 1985 Dec (Box 27:585)
        - Typescript draft, chapter 8, "Creating More Heroes", 1985 Dec 22 (Box 27:586)
        - Typescript draft, chapter 9, "Japan's Strategic Concept", 1985 Nov 25 (Box 27:587)
        - Typescript draft, chapter 9, "'More for More' in Practice", 1985 Dec 6 (Box 27:588)
        - Typescript draft, chapter 10, "A New Wave of Energy", 1985 Nov 26 (Box 27:589)
        - Typescript draft, chapter 10, "A New Role for Unions", 1985 Dec 22 (Box 27:590)
        - Typescript draft, chapter 10, "The Challenge to America's Comparative Advantage", 1986 Nov 25 (Box 27:591)
        - Typescript draft, chapter 11, "Creating More Heroes", 1985 Nov 27 (Box 27:592)
        - Typescript draft, chapter 11, "The Visible Hand", 1985 Dec 23 (Box 27:593)
        - Typescript draft, chapter 11, "The Stakeholder Strategy", 1986 Nov 25 (Box 27:594)
        - Typescript draft, Part I, "A Stakeholder Strategy for the Economy" (eleven chapters), 1986 Jan (Box 27:595-597)
        - Draft, Part I, 1986 Apr 25 (Box 27:598-601)
        - Draft, Part I, 1986 May (Box 27:602-604)